SWATI RAWAT

1122/4, Om Nagar, Unnao, Uttar Pradesh, 209801 ♠

9451866413 📞

rawatswaty98@gmail.com ► https://www.linkedin.com/in/swati-

rawat-13200a17bin



OBJECTIVE

Focused, Applied Economics major, currently attending Banaras Hindu University, with 7 months of work experience. Aiming to leverage a proven knowledge of energy efficiency, cost reduction, energy audits skills, to successfully fill the Energy Analyst role at your company. Frequently praised as hard working by my peers, I can be relied upon to help your company achieve its goals.



EDUCATION

Master's in Applied Economics | Banaras Hindu University
JULY 2019 - PRESENT

Bachelor's in economics | Banaras Hindu University

JULY 2016 – JULY 2019

CGPA-7.5

Higher Secondary in Science | Kendriya Vidyalaya, Unnao

Passed with 72.6%



EXPERIENCE

Finance Management | Vardhan Consulting Engineers- Patna, Bihar

(Work from Home)

SEPTEMBER 2019 - PRESENT

Internship Roles and Responsibilities:

Analytical learning, designing/modelling with techno-commercial detailing of Project Finance-Modelling and Analysis.

Policy Research | Vardhan Consulting Engineers- Patna, Bihar

(Work from Home)

MAY 2019 - AUGUST 2019

Internship Roles and Responsibilities:

Analytical learning and research and analysis on Govt. Policies on Renewable Energy sector, FDI and Transactions for India and other South-East Asian Countries (through their Online Portal).

Associate Project Manager | M R Impressions - Bhopal, Madhya Pradeh

(Work from home)

FEBRUARY 2019-APRIL 2019

Internship Roles and Responsibilities:

Understanding the mail chain and replying accordingly, survey making (according to client's requirements), setting the survey live and calculation of total cost.



- Time Management
- Report writing and analysis
- Documentation

- Research and trend analysis
- Statistical techniques
- Skilled in Microsoft Excel



ACTIVITIES

- Green Revolution Global Certification Program (Basic plus Advance level with A Grade)-International Centre for Culture & Education(ICCE) supported by United Nations Framework Convention on Climate Change (UNFCCC)
- Certificate of completion in Cooperate Skill Development Program- Vardhan Consulting Engineers
- Certificate Course in Yogic Practices for Better Living- Banaras Hindu University
- Certificate in Advance Self Defense Training Camp- 2018- Banaras Hindu University